Josuke, I'm going on a hunting trip. Huh?
And you're coming too.
Whoa there!
Hang on a second, Jojoro!
Run that by me again!
I could have sworn you
said we were going hunting!
If...
that's true...
Does that mean we're going hunting
for hotties with hot bodies?
Cause you should know, I'm a
little more the romantic type.
I'm not sure I'll be able to pull it off.
You'll have to show me the ropes.
I spoke to Otoishi. He confessed.
Are you serious?
Yeah, he had quite a lot to say.
Especially regarding the bow and arrow.
It turns out he also
used it to shoot a rat.
He did what?
That's right.
But the rat didn't die.
Even though it was writhing in agony,
it freed itself from the arrow
and made a break for the hills.
You know what that means.
Humans aren't the only organisms with
the potential to acquire stand abilities.
But we don't know what this rat can do,
so we have to hunt it
down before it lashes out.
I'll see you
soon.
That was awesome.
Those were just regular cans.
Keeping a nimble rat within
range won't be so easy.
Which is why we have these bearings.
They'll expand your range to 20 meters.
This should be obvious.
But they're useless against stands.
Use them when you're in
position to take down the user.
Give it a try.
I have to use them too.
You sure about this?
I don't even have the concentration.
for ball sports and stuff, you know?
Oh, I almost got it.
Not bad for a newbie.
I'd give it an 85.
But I need you to remember
one thing while on this hunt.
When dealing with live animals, you
have to prioritize composure over speed.
If you corner the rat
and screw up the shot,
don't expect it to be gullible
enough to come within range again.
So hold your fire until you
know you can hit your target.
One more thing, don't let
the pressure bog you down.
Got it?
Well, he sure knows how to
make a guy feel at ease.
From what he told me, Otoishi shot
the rat near this irrigation canal.
Given the location, it
was probably a brown rat.
Brown rats are agile swimmers.
Adaptable and can eat
practically anything.
Larger rats can grow up to
20 or 30 centimeters long.
And some can weigh as much as one kilogram
with a horizontal leap
of about two meters.
Found them. Huh?
You mean those aren't bird tracks?
Its four feet have four
digits and its hind feet five.
The S shape means it's dragging something.
These markings are tail tracks.
The rat's about 20 centimeters long.
I don't know how many, but
there are more than one here.
There's a tick on this leaf, which means
it's a stomping ground for rodents.
There's no question about it.
Somewhere in that drain is a nest.
For now, our best bet is to set a trap
and see what the video camera picks up.
That's one of those cameras that lets
you watch while you're recording, right?
You're not going to use
cheese for the trap?
It's a hunk of tempura.
Cheese is too luxurious for a common rat.
What's with all the flies?
Did something die?
Jojaro!
These are...
Those are dead rats!
Yeah, no shit!
Oh, it looks like a block of jellyfish!
Why the hell are you poking it?
It's flesh.
At some point, the flesh of these
rats melted and later congealed.
It seems as though the melting
started from under their flesh.
How in the world does something as
messed up as that even happen? Dunno.
If I had to guess, I'd say this is
the handiwork of the rat we're after.
So it stand at this?
That seems to be the case.
It took out its fellow rats to seize
the territory, which would mean...
It's highly likely the rat's
making a nest in that drain.
The question now is, has our culprit
used its powers to wreak any more havoc?
Looks like the drainage canal
continues on to that house.
It might already be too late.
You think it beat us here?
At first glance, I see a
chicken coop, but no chickens.
The cars are still parked in the garage.
and there doesn't appear to
be any activity in that house.
The front door is unlocked and open.
All signs point to the rat being inside.
It's safe to assume the owners of
this house have already been killed.
Let's go.
We have to investigate.
The rat will let us approach
it up to a certain point.
It's intelligent enough to know that most
humans are too slow to ever catch it.
So it's not expecting to
be used as target practice.
That's how we'll close in and put
an end to this mess with one shot.
Bingo.
These are rat droppings.
There's no grass or grain here.
Only meat.
The droppings lead to
that room. Come on. Right.
What?
It looks like an old
refrigerator compressor.
What the hell?
Am I going crazy or did the
refrigerator just open by itself?
Did the door's magnet
give out or something?
Holy shit, I found it!
That little bastard's right there!
I get it.
So that's what opened the fridge.
Nobody told me rats could
open refrigerator doors.
That doesn't make any sense.
Someone must have
forgotten to shut it. No.
Get real, Josuke.
You're not that gullible, are you?
This rat's a stand user.
Jo...
That's right.
Jotaro went into the next
room to look for the rat.
Freaking great now our eyes have met
How the hell the rat did this
They're still alive did
the rat disfigure the
owners of this house with
its stand so it have An
easier time storing them
in the fridge oh and
it's eating them damn it
Jotaro's not coming back!
I'll have to kill this thing myself!
When dealing with live animals, you
have to focus on composure over speed.
If I don't tag him on my first
try, he'll know my range.
Damn it, Jotaro!
I know you said no pressure, but still...
Of course, the table and chair are
positioned just enough to be in my way.
I have to make sure I sink this ball
bearing right between his beady little eyes.
Now, stay right there.
Oh, crap!
He stopped eating!
If I move closer, he'll run for it!
Forget this!
It's now or never!
I'll blast him from over here!
He's moving! Now!
I got him!
Shit, it wasn't a fatal blow!
Here we go!
That weird machine must be a stand!
Alright, pal, come and get some if you
think you've got what it takes to beat me!
Just know that my next shot is
gonna take you out for good.
Damn it, he's running under the table!
No, you don't!
Jotaro, what the hell are you doing?
The rat's in here!
That shape...
Not good!
His stand fires projectiles!
What now?
Should I slap it away with my bare hands?
No, that's disgusting!
Where's the rat?
Did I hit it with my ball
bearing or did I miss?
You bastard!
Yeah!
I got him after all!
It wasn't between his eyes like
I said, but he's still a goner.
That was a close one.
Hey, Jotaro!
Get over here!
I took out the rat!
The hunt is over!
Jeez, what were you doing in there?
You went missing right
when I needed you the most.
I was starting to think
you'd abandoned me.
But hey, at least it's dead.
Luckily, everything
went according to plan.
Well, for me, that is.
Our rat friend wasn't so fortunate.
Though his stand shot some
needle-like things at me.
Whatever they were, I bet they're
what turned your flesh to goo.
He got to the people who own this
place, but they're still alive.
I'll fix them right up
with Shining Diamond.
If we don't eliminate them by sundown,
things might get even messier.
Huh?
There was another rat, and
that one managed to hit me.
Jotaro, your hand is melting!
It happened in the other room.
I could have dodged the attack.
But I thought catching the needle
for analysis was the best choice.
All it takes is a touch
and it stands poison
begins to permeate even
melting other stands.
Five or six hits and you'll turn
into a quivering mass of flesh.
Oh good thing that needle didn't hit me.
Never thought I'd be
grateful for being squeamish.
The rat bolted out the door
after hitting me with the needle.
Somehow it must have figured out you
killed its kin here in the kitchen.
Um sorry to bother but would you
mind using your power to fix my hand?
Not to worry, just leave it to me.
Damn it.
Why those little SOBs have to multiply?
This is the Speedwagon
Foundation Research Department.
Hello, this is Jotaro.
Jokujo speaking.
Jotaro, finally!
We've tried to reach you several times.
I was hunting the rat
and had the ringer off.
Is this about Otoishi?
Yes.
Akira Otoishi was withholding the fact
that he shot two rats instead of one.
Are you sure?
Is there any chance he could
have shot three or four?
No, sir.
We're sure it's two.
Oh, good grief, Otoishi.
What a fool.
When it comes to its own territory, it'll
kill everything, humans and rats alike.
It cares only about itself.
So, this savage's time on Earth is
about to come to a fast end. Let's move.
Jotaro, hold on a minute, would you?
A pint-sized rodent just
ran into an open field.
How exactly do you plan on
tracking this thing down?
A famous artist, Ernest
Thompson Seton, once said,
There's not an animal on the
planet that cannot be tracked.
You have to know their habits.
Rats are known to avoid unfamiliar paths,
which means its root of escape had to
be that irrigation channel from before.
And there's something else about rats.
If they're not constantly eating,
they'll starve within a few hours.
There.
Those are fresh bite marks.
Nice going!
This is an awesome start!
Now we're gonna corner
that bucktooth bastard!
Take a look at this I don't think he even
gave a damn that our bait
was here he's on tape
Huh his ear looks like a bug-eaten leaf
what do you say we call him bug-eaten
He's being cautious this isn't
gonna be like at the house bug-eaten
is gonna be extra careful to not let
us skip within 20 meters of them.
We'll have to use these to finish the job.
Wait, those are real?
Yeah, they have to be.
Because of air resistance, ball
bearings lose accuracy when traveling
over 20 meters.
With a bullet nose like this, we'll be
able to hit our mark up to 70 meters away.
Will I have to launch that
with my stand's hand too?
Because I don't think I'm
ready for that just yet.
Point taken.
I'll have to be the one to do it.
Hold it right there.
Just what are you trying to say?
That comment didn't sit well with me.
I am the one who nailed the rat
back at the house, remember?
Sure, it wasn't exactly a
perfect shot, but still.
Guess you're right. Take two.
More pressure.
Be careful.
This puddle is full of leeches. What?
Shit.
So what's going on?
Be careful. Eyes up.
The footprints suddenly stop here.
You've got to be joking!
Why would they randomly stop like that?
I know.
He's under us.
He must have burrowed a
hole and covered himself.
No.
This is called backtracking.
I didn't know rats could do this, too.
Backtracking?
Backtracking is the way
in which a wild animal
reverses itself by
stepping in its own tracks.
This confuses predators long
enough for them to hide.
In Japan, the behavior has been observed
with brown bears, weasels, and rabbits.
However, it is unheard of
among rats and other rodents.
Okay, so let me get this straight.
You're saying that a common brown
rat pulled a fast one on us?
Things have taken a turn for the worse.
With this kind of terrain, the
hunters may have just become the prey.
I have this creepy feeling
we're being watched.
We better duck behind a rock
while we still have the chance.
No sudden movements.
The good news is Bug Eaton's attack
isn't too fast for us to see.
Just keep an eye out
for the point of fire.
If we can figure out where he's
hiding, we'll snipe him instead.
Son of a bitch!
That dirty rodent used our
own rat trap against us?
Star Platinum, the world!
Oh, good grief.
Don't worry I removed the
needle before the poison
spread along with all
the affected tissue you
should put a bandage on it
I was also able to locate
his general whereabouts
take a look he's halfway
up the hill near those
three rocks you found him
and helped me I don't know
who's more amazing you
are the rat compared with
the two of you I'm starting
to feel like I'm a kid
at the Grown-up's table.
It's 60 meters away.
So far, no sign of any more needles.
He knows a random firing
would give away his location,
and it's obvious he doesn't
want to be attacked.
He's a stubborn bastard.
Why are you praising that damn rat?
We need to act, and we have to do it now.
Well spoken, Josuke.
We need to give this assault
everything we've got.
or Bug-Eaten will kill us both.
All right, I'll give you all four rounds.
At this distance,
the rounds will rise like sliders, so
aim one centimeter below the target.
If I'm firing, what are you going to do?
I'm moving in so he'll shoot his needles.
Your job, Josuke, is to
determine his location.
Then, I'm counting on you to end this.
You want me to what?
You don't have a choice in the matter.
Even if one or two of his needles get me,
you can just use Shining
Diamond to heal me.
You can't heal yourself with that
power, so you get the kill shot.
This is our last stand.
Make it count.
Could I have a second to prepare?
Star Platinum! The world!
Did you find him? No.
As soon as he fired, he ran
off and hit somewhere else.
I'll try getting closer while
going up the side of the hill.
Wait for him to fire.
Yeah, will do.
Damn this pressure.
There! I see him!
What the...
That little shit-heel
predicted I'd dodge his
attack and fired the needles
at the rocks instead.
They ricocheted at me.
Jotaro, no!
Don't stand there gawking at me, Josuke!
Keep your eyes trained on the rat.
The moment he attacks, blow
his ass straight to hell!
This isn't good.
I've got four rounds,
but I'm out of chances.
If I waste even a single second?
Here we go, Josuke.
There!
He's in the same spot as the last time he
fired, but he's hiding behind the rocks.
Shit!
If only he was looking over here!
I've gotta do this.
I'll just have to hit a tiny target.
No problem.
I suddenly feel that fighting spirit.
Right then, it's time for you to die.
Shosuke Mists!
What do we do now?
There you are.
I knew my Mists would
make you turn around.
It's good to see that ugly face.
And right now, you're
right in my crosshairs.
Guess I can hang with
the grown-ups after all.
Call me Josuke Higashikata, the mighty
vanquisher of pressure and stress.
Akira's mutant stand rats got me thinking.
They are reflections of our
destruction of the environment.
I'm not sure how to feel.
But at least Josuke is a dependable guy.
Good grief.
Maybe now we'll all get
a little peace of mind.
Anytime I need to see a
face, I just close my eyes.
And I am taking two
bits with crystal mine.
And magenta, feeling me take a shelter.
In the face of my spine, straight
like a Chaka cherry cola.
I don't need to try to
explain, I just hold on tight.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly.
To the arms and the lips and the face
Of the human kind of all that I need to,
I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you?
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you, but ooh,
I've got to find out.
Ooh,
I want you, I don't know if I need
you, but ooh, I've got to find out.